[{"id":538,"question":"Choose the correct HTML tag for the smallest size heading?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<heading>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<h1>","answer_d":"<h6>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":887,"question":"What are Docker objects?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Docker images, containers and services","answer_b":"Files, Plugins and Base","answer_c":"Code, Databases and Local storage","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":125,"question":"Choose the correct HTML element for the largest heading:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<heading>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<h1>","answer_d":"<h6>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1013,"question":"What Is The Role Of Kube-scheduler?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kube-scheduler is responsible for assigning a port to newly created pods.","answer_b":"kube-scheduler is responsible for assigning a node to old created pods.","answer_c":"kube-scheduler is responsible for assigning a cluster to newly created pods.","answer_d":"kube-scheduler is responsible for discovering the newly created pod and selects an optimal node for them to run on","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":322,"question":"Just installed plugin crashes your Wordpress site with no access to the dashboard. What do you do?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Rename the specific plugin folder in /wp-content/plugins","answer_b":"Reinstall Wordpress","answer_c":"Delete all plugins from /wp-content/plugins folder","answer_d":"Reinstall the database","answer_e":"Rename the specific plugin folder in /wp-includes/plugins","answer_f":"Rename the specific plugin folder in /wp-admin/plugins"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":902,"question":"To create a new deployment in kubernetes, use the command","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubernetes set deployment","answer_b":"kubernetes get deployment","answer_c":"kubectl run","answer_d":"kubectl deploy","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":872,"question":"Which is not true about Docker Hub?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Docker Hub is the world's largest library and community for container images","answer_b":"Docker Hub provides an easy way to create, manage, and deliver your teams' container applications","answer_c":"Docker Hub is a totally private repository","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":748,"question":"The API server is also known as:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubeapi","answer_b":"kube-server","answer_c":"k8s-apiserver","answer_d":"kube-apiserver","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":694,"question":"Which command can be used to rename a file/directory?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"mv","answer_b":"cp","answer_c":"rename","answer_d":"rm","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":960,"question":"What is a cluster?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"A system made up of multiple servers and other resources","answer_b":"A computer program or device that provides services to other computers","answer_c":"A specific set of ordered operations","answer_d":"A software package that performs a specific function for an end user","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":714,"question":"What could be used to program additional authentication logic besides available authenticator modules?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Kube Vault","answer_b":"Authentication Proxy","answer_c":"Kube Auth Service","answer_d":"Kubernetes Role Manager","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"Using Authentication Proxy, the API server can extract the information it needs about the user’s identity using the HTTP headers that you specify. Let’s have a quick example to demonstrate this concept:","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":443,"question":"What is the HTML Tag for the largest heading","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<h6>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<h1>","answer_d":"<heading>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":888,"question":"How can you find the status of a Docker container?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The command “docker ps -a” is used for identifying the status of a Docker container.","answer_b":"The command “docker ps status” is used for identifying the status of a Docker container.","answer_c":"The command “docker ps -p” is used for identifying the status of a Docker container.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":571,"question":"PHP is an example of ___________ scripting language.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Server-side","answer_b":"In-side","answer_c":"Browser-side","answer_d":"Client-side","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1053,"question":"What is the Ansible setup module used for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Gathers facts about remote hosts","answer_b":"Setup Ansible on remote hosts","answer_c":"Setup ansible on a master host","answer_d":"Setup your SSH keys","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"DevOps"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"}]